#### Contact

sahil1996mahajan@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/harsh-mahajan-45645219a (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Research
Report Writing
Market Research

# Harsh Mahajan

Research Analyst / MBA (B.M) Narsee Monjee Delhi

## Summary

Experienced Analyst with a demonstrated history of working in the research and capital market industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, Market Research, Management, and Report Writing. Strong business development professional with a Master of Business Administration - MBA focused in Business Management, General from SVKM's Narsee Monjee Institute of Management Studies, Mumbai

## Experience

Cisive

Screening Associate (Database Analyst) April 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months)

New Delhi Area, India

Aegis Customer Support Services Private Limited Senior Executive July 2018 - March 2019 (9 months) gurugram

Magus Customer Dialog Executive July 2017 - June 2018 (1 year) New Delhi Area, India

### Education

SVKM's Narsee Monjee Institute of Management Studies (NMIMS) MBA, Business, Management, Marketing, and Related Support Services · (2018 - 2020)

#### Delhi University

Bachelor of Commerce - BCom, Business/Commerce, General · (2014 - 2017)

The Institute of Company Secretaries of India Certificate, capital market · (2015 - 2015)